I just click on generate and I wait until my image is generated.
My AI created image is generated.
Yep, so as you see, it takes some time.
And as you see, one of my credits is removed, so now I have five credits and over here in
my library, a number was added, so this library thing contains all of your previously
generated images, you know?
Everything that you do in for tour, you'll access it later on from this my library thing.
And as you see, the image that is generated is pretty high quality, wow, right?
So as you see, it does it very well with the generation and stuff.
It's very natural.
And perfect.
So as you see, this is what we have, we can download it using this button over here.